Britain 1939. Hitler's grip is tightening. No-one can be trusted.
Six Minutes to Midnight is a thriller, drama,
history film directed by Andy Goddard.
Summer 1939.
Influential families in Nazi Germany have sent their daughters to a finishing school in an English
seaside town to learn the language and be ambassadors for a future looking National Socialist.
A teacher there sees what is coming and is trying to raise the alarm.
But the authorities believe he is the problem.
Thomas Miller, played by Eddie Izzard.
Ilse Keller, played by Carla Juri.
Captain Drey, played by James D'Arcy.
Corporal Willis, played by Celyn Jones.
Colonel Smith, played by David Schofield.
Charlie, played by Jim Broadbent.
Six Minutes to Midnight is a 2020 British war drama film directed by Andy Goddard from a screenplay - loosely based on a true story -
by Goddard, Celyn Jones and Eddie Izzard, starring Izzard, Judi Dench, Carla Juri, James D'Arcy and Jim Broadbent.
Six Minutes to Midnight was released in the United
Kingdom on 26 March 2021, by Sky Cinema.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of united kingdom, macabre, somber, 1930s, absurd.
The tone is emotional and intense.